SHARON CHUKWUEMEKA

No. 24a Awkuzu Street, Lekki phase 1, Lagos

TEL: 08093944347.

Email: sharonnonye7@gmail.com@gmail.com@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Enthusiastic college student working towards attaining a degree. Experience across business communication channels including social media, email blasts and public relations. Quick-learner with positive attitude ready to make immediate impact. Prepared to contribute to organizational success while developing new skills and gaining real-world experience. Highly organized, responsible and well-versed. Positively impacts operations with top-notch communication and critical thinking skills.

KEY SKILLS

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Social media savvy
- English language fluency
- Problem solving abilities
- Project support
- Secretarial and administrative proficiency
- Team collaboration

EDUCATION:

Bachelor of Science: Food Science 2016 - Current

University of Ilorin, Ilorin, Kwara State

Secondary School: Sciences 2014

Federal Government Girls College, Owerri, Imo State

WORK EXPERIENCES

G-Tonia Foods – Industrial Training

06/2020 -12/2020

Responsibilities:

- Determined quantity of product to be prepared for daily operations.
- Marketed company product.
- Efficiently handled food processing equipment.

First Virgo Aluminium Ltd - Receptionist

07/2018 -11/2018

Responsibilities:

- Collected, sorted and distributed and sent email
- Answered telephone calls to field inquiries from clients, vendors and all other call seeking information.
- Wrote professional business documents.

OTHER RELEVANT INFORMATION

Technical Strengths:

Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel and PowerPoint).

Interests:

Traveling, Swimming, Video editing.